EAT THIS, PAL!
YOU'RE DEFENCELESS
UNDER MY COUNTER ATTACK!
YES, I WAS RIGHT, FF!
WHY IS SHE IN THIS DISCIPLINE, SELL?
IT'S A DISK!
Palesnake is here somewhere.
Shit, where is he?
No way.
He's who threw it?
Monster!
You try to tell me that
Palesnake is really...
I knew it.
You're full of poochie!
Thank
you
so
much for watching.
I don't wanna play.
Let's go, let's go!
One, two, three.
Can we find a way?
I want me.
I want you to be me.
To the top.
Break out.
We're coming out.
We're coming out. We're coming out.
I remember everything.
Since the day I met Jolene on the farm.
It's still so clear it might
as well have been yesterday.
The weird scribbles on the public phones.
The fluffed up blankets on the bed.
The stink of the trash.
The guards screaming and yelling.
The sound of the doors
opening and closing.
Hearing the toilets flushing all day long.
I even remember all those silly
talks with Jolene and everyone else,
laughing hysterically.
But still,
even though I lived at
the farm for many years,
I don't remember anything
from before that.
All I can pull from that time are
robotic thoughts, almost like recordings.
I simply followed orders,
and my task was to protect Palesnake's
disks without knowing or even asking why.
I finally understand now that
living is more than Just being
alive it means making memories
if I lose that I lose everything
Jolene takes all these actions
on behalf of her dad and risks
her life to help Aramis and
the few other people she trusts
because she has pleasant memories
from living her life that's
the remarkable thing about
humans their memories give their
souls courage the knowledge
that I am FF I never had that in
the past that's it I know it
that that is what intellect is
what's it going to be am I your
utmost priority or is it more
important to snuff out Dng's
life to try and save Jolene's
you hesitated it's too late
that moment will cost your life.
Do you even know why you have
your intellect and powers?
Because I gave them to you.
And now I'm taking them back.
When I need to kick up my courage,
I think about Jolene.
Those very things are memories.
And this, this is intellect.
W-what the hell?
It couldn't be.
What on earth did FF just do?
She infused them with her own body fluids!
No, I can't believe it.
Well, well.
It seems FF pulled it off.
They killed the user like
they said they would.
There's nothing inside the pod.
What the hell is that?
Does this mean that thing was born?
Is this what Pale Snake's
been after the whole time?
My god, what is it?
What purpose was it conceived to serve?
And why does it need to
be here specifically?
Were the prisoners turned into plants,
just so this thing could finally be born?
And what's even weirder is, I stopped
becoming a plant because it was born.
But I guess it doesn't matter anymore.
Don't you dare let FF get away from you!
Retriever disc and read
every memory on it!
Locate the warehouse of that thing born
from Dio's bone, and then go track it down.
I'm totally exposed.
It may not even last 30 seconds out there.
I need water.
I have to find a way to get back to Jolene
and tell her who Pale Snake really is.
Damn it.
She needs to know it's Father
Poochy, the friggin' chaplain.
Let me guess you're thirsty and
trying to go to the tap out front.
Well, before you hurry off, dear,
wait as I have quite an
important question to ask you.
I'm sorry, gotta go, but here's my answer.
Now about that question
I wanted to ask you, FF.
Well, are you listening to me?
Tell me the truth, I'm curious.
Did you happen to get a good look
at the miracle that was just
born in the discipline cells?
What kind of organism was it?
Was it animal or plant?
And was it beautiful?
You tell me something, what's a
priest like you doing at this prison?
I'm sure it isn't for anything noble.
Hush, I'm the one who's asking
the questions, thank you.
You see, if I simply take
your memories and read them,
I would know the nature of
what was born immediately.
However I would much rather
hear your personal account of
it because saying things such
as it was soft or it was a
strange color or it was lovely
or your self-generated thoughts
and not the memories actually
embedded within your disc I
get it you're worried that
thing is gonna run away and
disappear huh and you'd lose it
forever what are you saying it's
already moved maybe who knows
to be honest you should be way
more worried about it being
killed much less moved actually?
Only I take that back.
It might be dead already.
I mean, the guy Jolene is
with is kind of a dick.
I know he'd kill it if he
thought it was dangerous.
Killing it is not only
difficult, it's quite impossible.
There is no way.
It possesses far too much power
and strength to fall prey to that.
It's indestructible.
My concern is that Jolene
will get sidetracked
or do something rash and lose sight of it.
Only Jotaro's memories can
control what has been born.
That is what matters.
And I have those memories
in my clutches now.
We have finally come to the
point where we're one step away.
What was its bodily form like?
Did it develop quickly?
Did it show response to stimuli?
I thought if it hit the
water, it would drown.
Uh, what else?
Yeah, I don't quite remember.
Uh, okay, well, let's see.
She's stalling for time!
Quick, behind you!
I did it!
Oh, by the way, FF's intellect, its
control tower is nowhere near here.
It's that way!
Even better, I've got water now!
Which means I can go and
tell Jolene all of it!
Intellect, you say?
You're not the one who decides
where your intellect is.
These powers belong to someone else.
In fact, it's the one who graciously
gave you your stand powers with a disc.
Me.
You sent tin bag of plankton!
You're explaining things to me with
unearned triumph and arrogance?
How dare you!
What's happening?
My whole body feels
like it's burning away!
Something's wrong here!
Is this even water?
What the hell is coming out of there?!
You son of a...
Yes, of course it's
water, but it's boiling.
The highest temperature
all aquatic life on Earth
can withstand safely is about
89.6 degrees Fahrenheit.
I have placed a different stand power that
can boil water conveniently into this one.
So I'll repeat myself.
I'm the only one who can
decide where your intellect is.
Any water you touch
henceforth is instantly
and reliably going to
boil with your power.
Rachel!
I don't see it.
Where did it fall in?
Oh, hell.
Could it have drowned?
No. Look!
Wait a minute.
That thing has will.
If it's running away,
that must mean... No.
It might just be moving
by sentient instinct.
I don't know if it's a plant or what
it is, But I have to stop it now.
Because if Pale Snake gets a
hold of it, then we're fucked.
No, Jolene!
Stop, Jolene, wait!
Don't move, look down at the
rock that's right by your foot!
Listen, don't take another step.
Turn around and look at me.
It just rolled a bit and became a
boulder however you Jolene your size
No, wait, I said you
can't get too close to it.
Remember
Anastasia look at you what happened to
your height you're like so tiny now?
Anastasia talk to me
try to calm down Jolene!
By the way, how big is everything
looking from your perspective?
It's normal.
The same as earlier.
Hate to say, it looks like the only
one who shrank was you, Anastasia.
What's going on?
The baby looks completely
normal-sized from where I am, too.
Only the rock that
turned over became small.
Listen to me.
Do not move from that spot.
Stay right where you are.
You're back to your own size.
I guess that means that's what
this baby's powers can do?
In other words, when we
get too close to the baby,
then boom, we shrink to a
fraction of our real size.
I really have no idea.
Those questions are quite hard to answer.
Look, if I get half this
distance towards the baby,
my height accordingly gets cut in half.
Then of course I have to walk.
Twice as far.
Furthermore,
if I get a quarter of the way to it, then
the walk distance is multiplied by four.
Likewise, an eighth of the way
will make it eight times farther.
One thirty-second, one sixty-fourth,
one one hundred twenty-eighth.
If my body keeps getting smaller,
then the distance keeps multiplying.
The big question is,
under these circumstances will we
ever be able to reach that baby?
I think by its very
design, the answer is no.
No good.
There's only one way I'm going
to get my dad's memories back.
That's keeping the baby the
hell away from that asshole!
Jolene, no!
Sorry, but I'm going.
We'll think about it after
getting as far as we can!
Concentration.
That's it.
Jolene's ability to concentrate
or focus on one thing.
I'm probably here because I was
attracted to that very quality.
Such focus makes her even more beautiful.
Those eyes.
Someday,
mark my words, I'm going to have those
eyes look at me with that same intensity.
Stone Ocean!
Just a little more.
I know I can catch it!
No you can't Jolene pull
your threat back now
you're never going to
reach that baby so you've
got to let it go I refuse to accept that
there has to be an end
come on it's right there
hey what if I jump from right
here instead that could work
if I jump there's definitely
an end and that's the
ground end of story watch
I'm gonna land it Just fine!
Jolene, I beg you, do not!
I'm almost there.
The ground is so close, I got this!
I'm just about to touch it, yes!
What?
My thread!
Oh, now what?
What the hell is that?
I'm not sure, but could that
be the green baby's stand?
Damn it!
When am I going to hit the ground?
Shit, it's not just getting bigger,
but it's getting stronger, too.
And it's twice as big now.
Oh no, I think this stand came
out just so it could pull me in.
In order to not let me escape from
this world that's falling down.
How do I get out of this?
Stone Ocean!
Okay, if this really is the baby's power,
then I'll just have to catch the stand.
Because that means I've caught the user!
No, dammit! I'm getting smaller!
I'm gonna shrink down into nothing!
The end wasn't the ground, it
was the stand the whole time!
Diver Drive
so now we know the closer
you keep getting to
the baby the smaller you
become and before long
eventually you'll be nothing
alas it seems this baby
has an invincible stand we
still don't know yet why
it was born but it will
be an enemy one day in
fact this baby Jolene will
be your direct enemy but
wait a second if it's
invincible shouldn't that mean
all the more reason I
can't let palesnake have it
Oh shit!
Anastasia, hold on!
That baby threw the rock at us.
Does this mean it thinks
and knows how to reason?
Is it starting to recognize its
power and figuring out how to use it?
It's coming! Climb!
We're getting out of here
as fast as we can! Run!
We could chase that baby forever.
And it wouldn't matter because
we won't be able to reach it.
But at least with this quick
detour, we captured the stand.
Jolene, haven't you seen it yet?
Do you understand where you
and I just climbed toward?
I know I took a risk, but that baby
has intellect and curiosity, clearly.
It touched the bottle
I threw at it earlier.
I saw that anything it
touches won't change size.
So this bottle is going to
stay exactly as it is now.
If we can't catch it by chasing
it, we'll force it to chase us.
We've gotten to the bottle, and
the stand is now inside of it.
Now all we have to do is
make sure it can't get out.
Great. One thing.
Do you have any idea how the fuck
we're supposed to get out of here?
Did you think of that?
I have Diver Drive hiding in the bottle.
Specifically, inside its walls.
It's altering the mouth for us.
Now's our chance.
Charge right in!
We've caught it. We're safe.
The baby's stand won't be
able to get out from there.
It's getting around by rolling. Run!
It's moving the bottle!
Anastasia!
Stone Ocean!
No!
Be careful or you'll destroy the bottle!
It's worse to get captured
by it when it escapes!
Did it somehow calculate that this was
going to happen and rolled the bottle?
Dammit, how is this possible?
I told you not to break that bottle!
Come on!
If it stays like this, you're gonna...
Anastasia, what happened?
And why am I holding the baby?
For real what's going on it seems this
thing is very interested in the star
shaped birthmark on your left shoulder
I would even call it fixated something
about it touching you has enabled us to
return to our original size and if you
haven't noticed it has the same birthmark
in its shoulder too what is this thing
apparently it's known Jolene since before
hey so uh I think this little goblin
might be getting kind of attached to me
um what should i do it's bonding not good
there's no doubt in due time this
child will become her enemy all
i feel from this baby's powers is
menace and infinite darkness we
might need this thing to get back
your dad's disc from pale snake and
i know how important that is but
honestly we may have to kill it now
Although you think I cope
my head is filled with hope
of some place other than he
although you think I smile
inside and all the while
I'm wondering about my destiny
I'm thinking
about all the
things I'd like
to do in my life.
I'm a dreamer.
A distant dreamer.
Dreaming far away.
From today!
Thank you.
You